talismanonline.com 2018-10-31

# Talisman Online - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**MiraGame** (Miracle Castle / Xingwan) is dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our users. This Privacy Policy describes the ways we collect, store, use, and manage the information you provide in connection with our website at www.MiraGame.com or any MiraGame’s game or application provided on other websites or other third party sources. Please note that the scope of this Privacy Policy is limited to information collected by MiraGame through your use of the service.

By using the service, you are agreeing to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for periodically reading this Privacy Policy. If you use our service after we have updated this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that you have read the updated terms and consent to our revised privacy practices. Use of the service after changes are made to the Privacy Policy will be considered your consent to the new terms.

**Information Collected and Used**  
MiraGame's primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the service and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the service. MiraGame may use user information to analyze user behavior in MiraGame’s games. For example, MiraGame may analyze user information to determine how often a user plays a particular game, if a user purchases premium goods and other similar events.

We may collect both Personal and Non-Personal Information. Personal Information is defined as information about you that can be used to contact or identify you such as your name, email address, home address, and phone number. Personal Information does not include aggregate information, which is data we collect about the characteristics and activities of users of the service, from which any Personal Information has been removed. Non-Personal Information does not identify you personally and can include age, gender or interests. We may combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information and use this combination to improve your experience or to aggregate it with information collected from other users to improve or analyze our service. This privacy policy in no way limits or restricts our collection of aggregate information or of Non-Personal Information.

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, if you register for a game account on our website. When you visit our website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets MiraGame help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information**  
MiraGame does not share your Personal Information except as approved by you or as described below:  

  * With your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;
  * Agents and service Providers: MiraGame may engage other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf. Examples of these services include sending postal mail and e-mail to you and analyzing data. While these agents and service providers may have access to your Personal Information in connection with the performance of services for MiraGame, they may not use such information for any purpose other than providing such services to MiraGame.
  * Protection of MiraGame and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our rights; or protect the rights, property, or safety of MiraGame our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.
  * Corporate Transfers and Financings: MiraGame may share your Personal Information in connection with any merger, sale of MiraGame assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
  * Aggregate Information: MiraGame may share aggregate information about you and/or your customers with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

**Links and Third Party Tools**  
The service may contain links to other websites. The fact that the service links to a website or presents a banner ad or other type of advertisement does not mean that MiraGame endorses or authorizes that third party, nor is it a representation of our affiliation with that third party. MiraGame is in no way responsible for the privacy policies of these other websites to which you chose to access from the service. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of those websites when exiting the service. 

**Security**  
We have put in place reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your Personal Information for improper purposes. Also please note that email and messaging systems are not considered secure, so we discourage you from sending us Personal Information through these mediums. 

**International Transfer**  
We may transfer information that we collect about you, including Personal Information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information, including Personally Information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. and the use and disclosure of information about you, including Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Policy Regarding Children**  
The service is not geared toward children under the age of 14 and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 14. If we learn that a child under 14 has provided us with Personal Information we will delete such information from our files. 

**No Guarantees**  
While this Privacy Policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet these standards, MiraGame does not guarantee that it will comply with these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, we offer no warranties or representations regarding the maintenance or non-disclosure of data. 

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@miragame.com](mailto:support@miragame.com).
